Lishi Nishod

Software Analyst

Wells Fargo, Bangalore, INDIA, 560103

INFO

Phone 9425984304 / 8073638281

E-mail lishinishod@gmail.com

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/ lishi-nishod-a06932b3

SKILLS

- Fluent in C, C++
- DataStructure & Algorithms
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Angular JS
- C#
- MYSQL
- Agile/ Scrum methodology
- Time Management
- Debugging and analysis

An accomplished software engineer specialising in object oriented design and analysis with experience in .Net and web development techniques. A strong team player with an emphasis on providing quality technical work in a timely manner. Versatile, quick learner, willing to embrace new challenges able to rapidly adapt to changes in requirements and innovations in programming languages.

EXPERIENCE

2017-02 - **Software Analyst**Present **Wells Fargo**

- Working on UI application, which is basically for risk, pricing and analysis of trade for equity derivatives.
- Modified existing application to correct errors and improve performance.
- Developed code fixes and enhancements for inclusion in future code releases and patches.
- Developed new features for the existing application.

2016-07-2017-02 Analyst Programmer Ramco System

- Worked in the field of application programming, design of function and programming.
- Fixing defects (internal and customer) in software application against requirement specification.
- Front end and backend designing of software application.

EDUCATION

2012-07-	National Institute of Technology, Bhopal
2016-04	 B.Tech in Computer Science
	• 7.45 CGPA
2011	Senior Secondary School Certificate
	77.76 % Marks in CBSE boards
2009	Secondary School Certificate
	80% Marks in CBSE boards

PROJECT

Title- Ride Solution

Java based desktop application where user can find details about buses of Bhopal (i.e. route, bus no. and fare for the journey) by providing source and destination and one can get the tourist places of Bhopal.

ACTIVITIES & ACHIEVEMENTS

- Earned appreciation of US counterpart for working on a component in Wells Fargo.
- Active member of ERT in Wells Fargo.
- Won 1st prize in group dance competition in Ramco.
- Solve programming problems on Code Chef with handler bitu.
- Participated in speed math's workshop, Technosearch 2012.
- Organising committee member of Abhivyakti event, Technosearch, 2013
- Event coordinator in college techfest "TECHNOSEARCH -2013".
- Secured 3rd position in treasure hunt of Technosearch.